glance.net 2019-06-30

# Glance Networks, Inc. - Glance Networks Inc

### This website is operated by Glance Networks, Inc.

Glance Networks, Inc. and its affiliates (“Glance” or the “Company”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit Glance’s Websites (“Visitors”), individuals who register to use Glance’s Services as defined below (“Customers”), and individuals who are authorized by Customers (“Subscribers”) to use the Glance Platform and related services (the “Services”). All users, whether Customers, Subscribers or Visitors are also referred to as “User” or “you” or “your.”

This Privacy Policy covers how Glance collects, uses, receives, retains, discloses and transfers, including international disclosure and transfer, (collectively “processes” or “processing”) Personally Identifiable Information or Personal Data (“Personal Information”) on www.glance.net and other web sites ending in glance.net (the “Website” or “Site). This Policy also describes your choices regarding use, access, deletion and correction of your Personal Information. This Policy applies to data collected online and offline.

Personal Information includes information about you that is personally identifying such as your name, email address, and phone number and which is not otherwise publicly available. Personal Information may include other types of information as well such as location data, your Internet Protocol (IP) address or other unique identifier, depending on the definition that applies in your physical location. Only the legal definition of Personal Information that applies in your location will apply to you under this Privacy Policy.

### Agreement and Affirmative Consent

**By using this Site and/or the Services, you accept and hereby expressly, explicitly and unambiguously consent to our processing of your Personal Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to check the most recent modification date to ensure that you are aware of any changes in our processing of your Personal Information. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Your continued use of the Site or Services after any changes signifies your express and unambiguous consent to any such changes. If you do not agree to such changes, you must immediately stop using the Site. This Privacy Policy was last modified on January 18, 2018.

### EU-US Privacy Shield and Swiss-US Privacy Shield

This privacy policy and Glance comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles and the United Kingdom and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles (the “Principles” or “Privacy Shield Principles”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, disclosure, transfer and retention of Personal Data from the European Union and Switzerland to the U.S. Glance commits to subject to the Principles all Personal Data received from the EU in reliance on the Privacy Shield.

By adhering to the Privacy Shield Principles, Glance agrees to be subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

As a Privacy Shield Organization, Glance has responsibility for the processing of Personal Information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Glance shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such Personal Information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Glance proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

To view the Glance certification on the Privacy Shield list, learn more about the Privacy Shield Principles, or view the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield website, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome>.

### Information Collection and Use

#### _Customers_

When Customers purchase the Services, Customers provide certain information, such as number of employees, company name and industry. We use the information to populate online profiles for Subscribers on the Site.

Glance Customers may submit data or information to the Services for hosting and processing purposes (“Customer Data”). In accordance with the Glance Services Agreement (i.e., Terms of Service), Glance may access Customer Data only for the purpose of providing the Services, preventing or addressing service or technical problems, at a Customer’s or Subscriber’s request in connection with customer support matters, or as may be required by law.

#### _Subscribers_

Customers provide name, phone number, email addresses, and other information to Glance for each Subscriber they authorize. Glance collects Subscribers’ IP addresses, usage data, and may also collect name, phone number, email addresses, and other information when Subscribers use Glance. Glance uses this information to provide access to the Glance Platform and authorized Customer content, to manage accounts, to respond to inquiries, to populate Subscriber profiles, and to send account-related and promotional email messages.

#### _Visitors_

When Visitors join sessions at the invitation of Subscribers, Glance collects Visitors’ IP addresses, and may collect those Visitors’ name, email address, and other information. Glance uses this information to provide access to the Glance Platform and authorized Customer content, to manage accounts, to respond to inquiries, to populate Subscriber profiles, and to send account-related and promotional email messages. Glance also furnishes Visitor information to the Customer who invited them to sessions.

Any recipient may unsubscribe from promotional emails by clicking “unsubscribe” on the bottom of the emails you receive from Glance.

#### _All Users_

When you download an ebook from the Site, we collect your first and last name, email address, and phone number. When you download a knowledge brief or contact us through our contact form on the Site, we collect your name, phone number, email, company, industry and number of employees. When you sign up for a free trial we collect your name, company, email, phone number and password. When you subscribe to updates, we collect name and email address. We also collect an IP address from all Users who access the Site.

We use the information we collect to provide the requested services and information, to respond to your inquiries and to send you promotional messages. You can opt out from promotional emails by clicking “unsubscribe” in the emails you receive from us.

### Choice and Consent

It is always your choice whether or not to provide us with Personal Information. If you do provide Personal Information to the Site, you are giving your express, explicit and unambiguous consent to the processing of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you choose not to provide the requested information you may not be able to access certain features on our Site or the Glance Platform. You may access, change, modify or delete your information, at any time, as described below.

We do not disclose your Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. You may also opt out in the event we use your Personal Information for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you.

You may access, update or correct your Personal Information by emailing a request to us at [privacy@glance.net](mailto:privacy@glance.net). In addition, upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your Personal Information. We will respond to your request in accordance with the law that applies to you.

Some users have certain rights regarding their Personal Information, depending on the nation and state in which they reside For example, if you are an EU resident, you may revoke your consent, obtain a copy of your Personal Information that we collect and have it transferred to another data controller, request erasure of your Personal Information, restrict the processing of your Personal Information, opt out of or object to certain processing activities such as profiling and automated processing decisions, and/or object to or block processing of the Personal Information you provide to us. To exercise any of these rights, you must email a request to us at [privacy@glance.net](mailto:privacy@glance.net). We will respond to your request in a reasonable timeframe and in accordance with the law that applies to you.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

When you visit the Site, we use “cookies.” These are pieces of information stored on your web browser temporarily, to allow us to uniquely identify your browser while you are browsing or interacting with the Site. Cookies also help us confirm your identity and are required in order to log into your account. If you wish to prevent cookies from being used as you navigate our Site, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies and/or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

Users who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Site, but will not be able to access or take advantage of all of the features and services on the Site. We therefore recommend you do not block or disable these cookies. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been sent and how to manage, as well as delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

As you navigate the Glance Website, Glance may also collect information through the use of commonly used information-gathering tools, such as Web Beacons (“Web Site Navigational Information”). Web Site Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Glance Websites (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked).

### Web Beacons

Glance may use Web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about Customers, Subscribers’ and Visitors’ usage of Glance’s Websites and interaction with emails from Glance. Web Beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular Website tied to the Web Beacon, and a description of a Website tied to the Web Beacon. For example, Glance may place Web Beacons in marketing emails that notify Glance when you click on a link in the email that directs you to one of Glance’s Websites. Glance may use Web Beacons to operate and improve Glance’s Websites and email communications.

### Data Retention

We will retain the information your provide for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Protection of Your Information

We will take appropriate physical, technical and organizational safeguards to protect Personal Information from theft, other loss, misuse, and any unauthorized access, copying, collection, use, disclosure, alteration or destruction. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

Any information that you give us is protected by a password for added security. Within Glance, your information is stored in password-protected, limited-access servers. Wherever possible, Glance servers reside behind firewalls that maintains tight controls on any access to the system from both our internal network and the Internet. Employees are made aware of our Privacy Policy and are trained on procedures to handle privacy-related concerns.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We do not retain visitor information for longer than 6 months. We will retain the Personal Information of a Subscriber for as long as you remain a Subscriber. We will retain and use Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We disclose the Personal Information of a Customer’s Subscribers to the Customer. We disclose the Personal Information of our users to third party vendors who help us operate the Site. These third parties are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information consistent with the terms of this Policy and to comply with the applicable data protection laws.

We will disclose your information in response to valid legal process, for example, in response to a court order, a subpoena or other legal request for information, and/or to comply with applicable legal and regulatory reporting requirements. We also may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our products and/or services and with applicable laws, or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer your information to an entity or individual that acquires, buys, or merges with Glance, or our other business units.

Glance is required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In the events above, you will be notified via email of such disclosure, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, in accordance with applicable law.

### Business Partners

From time to time, Glance may partner with other companies to jointly offer products or services. You may opt in to share your Personal Information with our business partners if you choose to purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly offered product or service. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may choose not to purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly offered product or service.

### International or Cross-Border Transfer of Your Personal Information and Your Express Consent

Given that the Internet operates in a global environment and that transfer of your data is necessary to provide you with requested Services, to provide updates, and to respond to your inquiries, using the Internet to collect and process Personal Information necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international, or cross-border, basis. By providing Personal Information and/or by communicating with us by email, you acknowledge and expressly consent to our processing and disclosure of your Personal Information in this way. The Personal Information of users who are located outside the U.S. may be transferred outside of each eligible country to the U.S., where our servers are located and where it will be processed and stored on servers in the U.S. In addition, the servers and storage we use to provide you services are provided by Cloud vendors (primarily Amazon Web Services, but possibly other vendors as well). Your personal information is stored there. Although the Privacy Shield Principles have been recognized as adequate, the U.S. has not been recognized as providing an adequate level of protection according to EU or Swiss data protection requirements, but we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that users’ Personal Information is treated securely in respect of such transfer and as described in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with the Principles. **By accessing the Site, using the Services, providing Personal Information or sending us email, you expressly, explicitly and unambiguously consent to such transfer, processing, storage and disclosure in countries outside the EU.**

Notice to Swiss residents: It is also possible that U.S. authorities may access data that is transferred to the U.S.  Glance will undertake to support affected data subjects to exercise their rights vis-à-vis foreign authorities in any way possible.

### Social Media Features

Our Site includes features from third party social media websites such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube and LinkedIn that run on our Site. Please note that our Site is not sponsored or endorsed by any of these social media sites, which are trademarked and owned by third parties and not by us. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features is governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.

### Links to Other Sites; Transactions with Third Parties

Please note that at some of Glance’s partner or advertiser properties, users may be asked to register and provide personally identifiable data directly to a third party partner or advertiser. When you do so, you are providing information to a third party and not to Glance. Accordingly, the collection and use of such Personal Information is controlled by the policies found on those sites. Since Glance cannot control those third party sites, we recommend that you take appropriate steps to control the use of Personal Information on third party sites.

Glance is not responsible for and will not be a party to any transactions between you and a third party provider of products, information or services. Glance does not monitor such transactions or ensure the confidentiality of your Personal Information, including credit card information, for any third party transaction. Any separate charges or obligations you incur in your dealings with these third parties linked to Glance’s Site are solely your responsibility.

### Children’s Privacy

Our site is directed to individuals who are the age of majority or older in their jurisdiction. We do not knowingly collect information from children. If you believe your child has provided information to the Site please contact us using the information provided below.

### Your California Privacy Rights; California Do Not Track Disclosures

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to our privacy officer as listed below. We currently do not honor Do Not Track signals.

### Accessing Your Information

_For Non-EU Users:_ You may at any time review or change your Personal Information by going to your account settings (if applicable) or contacting us using the contact information below. Upon your request, we will deactivate or delete your account and contact information from our active databases. Such information will be deactivated or deleted as soon as practicable based on your account activity and accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law.

_For EU-Users:_ EU Users may access their Personal Information that we hold in order to correct, amend or delete information that is inaccurate or has been processed in violation of the Privacy Shield Principles. We may charge a fee to provide this information. A user may submit an access request in writing to: [privacy@glance.net.](mailto:privacy@glance.net)

### Dispute Resolution for Complaints

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Glance commits to resolving complaints about your privacy and our collection, use or transfer of your Personal Data. Users with a complaint about our Policy should first contact Glance at [privacy@glance.net](mailto:privacy@glance.net) for resolution.

Glance has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent recourse mechanism, the International Center for Dispute Resolution/American Arbitration Association (ICDR/AAA), operated by the American Arbitration Association.

If EU or Swiss Users do not receive a response to a complaint within 45 days, or if the complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Glance, EU and Swiss Users should visit the ICDR/AAA EU Privacy Shield web site at <http://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html> to obtain information or to file a complaint at no cost. In the event the complaint of an EU or Swiss User is not completely resolved by Glance or by our independent recourse mechanism, EU and Swiss Users may invoke binding arbitration of the remaining dispute by contacting ICDR/AAA.

### Security Policy

Glance values work done by security researchers in improving the security of our products and service offerings. We are committed to working with this community to verify, reproduce, and respond to legitimate reported vulnerabilities. We encourage the community to participate in our responsible reporting process.

If you are a security researcher and would like to report a security vulnerability, please send an email to [security@glance.net](mailto:security@glance.net). Please provide your name, contact information, and company name (if applicable) with each report. Priority will be granted to encrypted reports – please include your PGP public key with such reports.

### Responsible Disclosure Guidelines

We will investigate legitimate reports and make every effort to quickly correct any vulnerability. To encourage responsible reporting, we commit that we will not take legal action against you or ask law enforcement to investigate you if you comply with the following Responsible Disclosure Guidelines:

  * Provide details of the vulnerability, including information needed to reproduce and validate the vulnerability and a Proof of Concept (POC)
  * Make a good faith effort to avoid privacy violations, destruction of data and interruption or degradation of our services
  * Do not modify or access data that does not belong to you
  * Give us a reasonable time to correct the issue before making any information public

We will attempt to respond to your report within 1-2 business days.

### Contact Us

If you have questions or suggestions, or wish to correct your Personal Information, please email us at [privacy@glance.net](mailto:privacy@glance.net)  
You may contact us at:

**Glance Networks, Inc.**  
Web Privacy Concerns, Attn: Privacy Officer  
1167 Massachusetts Avenue  
Arlington, MA 02476  
USA

1-877-GLANCE-ME  
(1-877-452-6236)  
Email: [privacy@glance.net](mailto:privacy@glance.net)

### Terms of Service

Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://ww2.glance.net/terms/>
